{
    "id": "8d4c8af937824dd991996225dbf4ddde",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather read a book ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "then watch TV",
                "than watch TV",
                "than to watch TV"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "425ccdec1a8a400aafd431878c9aaadf"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. she goes, she is surrounded by crowds of people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whoever",
                "Wherever",
                "Whichever"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "77938ed7c93645789e3f7c1a434140a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither the manager nor the workers …………………. guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3aa6bca550fd440a82a749ccd088102d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know James ………………….. father teaches at the academy?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9f1d523bfb33444591bd16b80a99939a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hardly had they heard the gunshots, ………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than they started running",
                "when they started running",
                "then they started running"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cceae8068e954085b8e479c6a8142fc1"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had two cars, I ………………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will sell one",
                "would sell one",
                "would have sold one"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "918fc262eed74daaa914d249d104ac07"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. she is rich, she is not happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "80e397ceea7445e7828354ce7842f048"
        },
        {
            "question": "You and I can do it, ………………… ? Add question tag.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't I",
                "can't you",
                "can't we"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "de674e0d455c4f6ea63b82cbb820af8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "A person who writes or compiles a dictionary is a ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "biographer",
                "author",
                "lexicographer"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9f4bc8e6d4f149e9979c41f7b4802c0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old parents ………………….. for a letter from their son for two months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are waiting",
                "has been waiting",
                "have been waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a64e470834394f0bbbdbb52df9cf37c8"
        }
    ]
}